megachords.com 2019-03-05

# JamPlay.com Privacy Policy

### Effective Date: August 16th, 2017

### Information about our Organization and Web site

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like JamPlay LLC ("JamPlay"). We are based in the United States, and our principal activity distributing guitar lessons via online videos and teaching tools. Our privacy policy covers JamPlay, LLC the www.JamPlay.com website. This privacy policy describes how JamPlay, LLC collects and uses the personal data you provide on our web site: http://www.jamplay.com.

It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal data and how you can access and update this information.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

Organization Name:| JamPlay, LLC  
---|---  
Address: | 1905 Woods Dr Ste 101  
City, Zip:| Beavercreek 45432  
State:| OH  
Country:| United States  
Controller: | JamPlay, LLC  
Web Sites(s):| www.JamPlay.com  
  
### Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

### The services and links of our Web site

Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data.

### Data Collection

When signing up for the site we collect the following personal data such as your name, email address and physical address. Additionally, we collect sensitive financial data from you, such as your credit card number.

When signing up to the Affiliate Program, we collect the following personal data such as email address, Tax ID and SSN. We use the information to coordinate your payouts and tax reporting. 

### Public Profiles

The profile you create on our site will be publically accessible unless otherwise indicated. You may change the privacy settings of your profile through your account portal.

### Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality. 

### Tracking technologies

Jamplay and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. 

### Behavioral Targeting/Re-targeting

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Data Collection and Purpose Specification

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

  * We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.
  * We may provide your personal data to companies, such as our payment processors, that provide services to help us with our business activities such as billing or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal data only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * We use your personal data to provide services to you. Credit card data is collected for the use of memberships. We also use this data to send updates to our sites and marketing communications. You can opt out of receiving promotional email by following the directions included in emails or by using your account settings page. We will share your personal data with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.
  * We do not sell your personal data to third parties.
  * If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected.

### Data Retention

We will retain your personal data for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us, if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your data to provide you services. We will retain and use your data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children or collect data from anyone under the age of 13.

### Disclosure and Visitor Choice

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations.

### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you want to update or delete your testimonial, please contact us.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of JamPlay. If you submit personal data to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policy. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

### Public Forums & Blogs

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums that you can comment via a third party application or directly from the site. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal data from our blog or community forum, please contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal data, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. You will need to contact or login into the third party application if you want the personal information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please review their privacy policy.

### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

### Confidentiality / Security

The security of your personal data is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal data submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us.

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process and other regulation. When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

In certain situations, Jamplay may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

### Privacy Compliance

There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation.

Primary personal data/Business information: 

  * Volunteered by each visitor? Yes
  * Collected from public records or bodies? No
  * Collected from private organizations

If JamPlay LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal data, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal data. 

### Privacy Support

Upon request Jamplay will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If you wish to access your personal data, update, delete, or have an enquiry about our privacy policy, please contact us:

  * sending an email to support@jamplay.com
  * calling us at 1-877-999-4526

We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. 

### Notification of Privacy Policy Changes

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
